<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>My Blog</title>
        <link>https://shobhitsugumar.github.io/</link>
        <description>This is my cool site</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:08:55 &#43;0530</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://shobhitsugumar.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>ABOUT ME</title>
    <link>https://shobhitsugumar.github.io/posts/first/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:08:55 &#43;0530</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://shobhitsugumar.github.io/posts/first/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Eager and driven engineering graduate with a passion seeking a challenging internship opportunity. Excited to engage in hands-on projects and collaborate with industry professionals to further develop technical expertise and contribute to innovative solutions. Aspiring to leverage academic knowledge and problem-solving skills to make a meaningful impact on cutting-edge engineering initiatives.
Projects Estimation of Crop Progression This a web based project which is an open discussion portal providing solution to farmers .]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Data Structure &amp; Algorithm</title>
    <link>https://shobhitsugumar.github.io/posts/second/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:02:55 &#43;0530</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://shobhitsugumar.github.io/posts/second/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[A data structure is a method of organizing data in a virtual system. Think of sequences of numbers, or tables of data: these are both well-defined data structures. An algorithm is a sequence of steps executed by a computer that takes an input and transforms it into a target output.
Together, data structures and algorithms combine and allow programmers to build whatever computer programs they’d like. Deep study into data structures and algorithms ensures well-optimized and efficient code.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Git &amp; GitHub</title>
    <link>https://shobhitsugumar.github.io/posts/third/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 11:02:55 &#43;0530</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://shobhitsugumar.github.io/posts/third/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Click to create an account https://github.com/
What is Git? Git is a modern and widely used distributed version control system in the world. It is developed to manage projects with high speed and efficiency. The version control system allows us to monitor and work together with our team members at the same workspace. Git is foundation of many services like GitHub and GitLab, but we can use Git without using any other Git services.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>SQL And DBMS</title>
    <link>https://shobhitsugumar.github.io/posts/fourth/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 11:02:55 &#43;0530</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://shobhitsugumar.github.io/posts/fourth/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[*SQL - Structured Query Language.SQL is a programming language used by nearly all relational databases to query, manipulate, and define data, and to provide access control. SQL was first developed at IBM in the 1970s with Oracle as a major contributor, which led to implementation of the SQL ANSI standard, SQL has spurred many extensions from companies such as IBM, Oracle, and Microsoft.
Sql is used to perform CRUD operatioins. Creat Read Update Delete What is DataBase?]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
